Hello guys, I'm welcome back. So now in this video, what we're going to do is we're going
to add the zombie characters a white. So the first thing which we need to do is to choose
the zombie's characters a white. So if you have some other zombie characters, then you
can use them. But if you want, you can use the characters, which is freely available
on maximum.com website white. So I'm going to show you how you can download the characters
from this website for our current project. Right? So as you can see, there are many scary
characters, but of course, we need these zombies. So I'm just going to start from this
one, okay, which is prisoner P type, Perry, I don't know which name is really complicated.
So I'm just going to use this character. And in order to download it, you just have to
click on the download button, then change it's supposed to original pose. And then you
can change the FBX forward to FBX for Unity. All right. And then you can just go ahead
and click on download. All right. The next character, which we will be using is this Romero
character, which is loading. Okay, it is this character. So you can go ahead and download
this character as well. Just click on download and the options are now already set up. So
you can click on the download button to download it. All right, after this, the next zombie
will be this one, which is war zone F actually war zone B F. And whatever its name is,
you can go ahead and download this in the same format as well. All right, after this, the next
zombie will be let's scroll down. Okay, it will be this female character zombie, which is zombie
girl. All right, go ahead and download this character as well. And then the next zombie will
be the police zombie, where it is. I think we skip it. So if we get back to the first page,
okay, it is right here, the cop zombie. All right, so you can just type cop zombie in the search
and it will show this character. All right, you can go ahead and download this zombie as well.
All right, after downloading it, get back to the project and in the game assets, let's go ahead
and create a new folder by the name of zombies. All right, and in this folder, I'm going to
drag and drop all of the six zombies. All right, all of these zombies will be like this. So we
need to do some changes. The first change is to change its rig. So you can select your zombie.
Okay, I've named them zombie one, two, three, four, five, six. Okay, you can select its rig and
change it to humanoid and then create from this model. And then you can click apply. All right,
you can do the same step for the other five zombies as well. Okay, just select all of these zombies
change its rig to humanoid and then click apply. That is all you have to do for all of these zombies.
Okay, for this zombie, it will show this error, which is rib is missing. So if you click on configure
right here, as you can see its arm is missing. And the reason the arm is missing because this zombie
doesn't have any arm. Okay, it's one arm is cut. So we need to fix this. So in order to fix this,
the left arm is fully right there. And in the left arm, if you notice, the lower arm is the
left forearm and the hand is left hand. But if you check the right arm for the right arm, the lower
arm and the hand is missing. So we need to add the same thing right here. But for the right hand.
So if you check the right hand, okay, left hand, pinky, okay, this is left, then let me find the
right to guess right shoulder. This is the health. Then this is the right shoulder. Okay,
here it is. So right arm, right forearm. Okay, so this right forearm, you can drag and drop
it right there. And then for the hand, you can drag and drop this right hand right there. Okay,
when you do that, then you can click on apply and then done. And now as you can see, the area is gone.
Now for this zombies fixed, okay, the other zombies are good to go now. As you can see, there
are no texture on these zombies. So for that, you can click on its material and then click on extract
texture. And it will open up the zombies folder. But in the zombies folder, let's create a new
folder. I'm going to name this as texture. And then open up the texture folder and then click on
select folder and then click on fix now. It is fixed. Let me move that there, click on scene view.
Let's start, click on FPS. It is our character. Let's move this. The Android 19 inside the player
related. Trying to drop this zombie. It is right here. If you notice the zombie height is a little bit
huge, then the player, but we just resize the zombie. But first, let's extract its
materials as well. So for the materials, I'm going to create a materials folder and in here, I'm going
to just extract it. Then you can do the same for the other zombies. Okay, extract its texture
in the texture folder. Click on fix now. Then for the materials, select the materials folder.
Okay, we're going to do the same step for the other zombies. I'm going to do it and then show
you. Guys, just make sure that you first extract the textures, then the materials are right.
Or else it will mess up the materials. So just do the same thing as I'm doing extract textures
and then extract materials. So once you are done doing all of this stuff, let's change to the
drum so that we see the zombie. As you can see, the zombie is a bit shiny. So if you select
all of these zombies materials, you can make the smoothness zero. Okay, now as you can see,
it looks good. Now let's try and drop all of these zombies and let's resize them. Okay, one by one.
So I'm going to try and drop all of these zombies in there.
Okay, so every material is fixed as we can see. Now let's delete it. Let's start from the first zombie.
Oops, I think we, I think I accidentally download this actual character. So I'm just going to
delete that. Okay, and also delete this character. So for that, we have just five zombies.
I will just skip the naming for now and let's try and drop this zombie.
Let's try to resize it. So I'm just going to click on its model and I'm going to make the scale
factor 0.9. Yep, 0.9 is good. Now delete it. Try and drop this zombie for this. I'm going to use 0.9 as
well. Yep. Then we have this female zombie for this 0.9 as well. Then we have this zombie. I think
this zombie size is good. So we can just skip that and this zombie size is good as well.
So we can skip that as well. Okay, so once we have all of these zombies set up now in the next
video, what I'm going to do is I'm going to make all of these zombies work. Okay, they will be able
to roam around in the environment and when they hear or see the player, they will try to attack
and kill the player. Okay, so catch you guys in the next one.